https://www.nutiva.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to main content
Free Shipping on orders over $49!
Privacy Policy No nonsense summary
Your information is kept private and handled securely.
Your email address will not be shared, sold or rented.
If you subscribe to our periodic newsletter, you can safely unsubscribe at any time.
The following is the full version of our policies:
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
Credit card information will only be retained for the duration required to process (approve/decline) an online order. Credit card information is Not stored in our systems for future use.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
Collection of Email addresses will only be used for the normal processing of orders, and if chosen by the visitor, for the purpose of sending occasional information in the form of an email newsletter.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
Newsletter
Get the Scoop
Enter your email below to get delicious recipes, promotions and product updates delivered right to your inbox!
Back to Top
